<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Indecisive RPS</string>
    <string name="playing_for">Playing For: %s</string>
    <string name="what_s_your_move">What\'s your move?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_decisions">Your decisions</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="title_activity_social">Your social stuff</string>
    <string name="rpsimageview_description">Diagram of Rock Paper Scissors rules</string>
    <string name="about_indecisive_rps">About Indecisive RPS</string>
    <string name="settle_important_dilemmas">Settle important dilemmas like \'tacos or pizza\' by
        playing Rock Paper Scissors with a friend or against the app!
    </string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an account to play with a friend and record your
        decision history, or just play a quick round without logging in
    </string>
    <string name="the_app_will_take_care_of">The app will take care of assigning (and, more
        importantly, remembering) who gets which option
    </string>
    <string name="no_more_debates">No more debates along the lines of \'Wait, were you tacos or was
        I?\'
    </string>
    <string name="just_play_a_round_and_move_on_to_the_important">Just play a round and move on to
        the important tasks of taco (or pizza) acquisition and consumption
    </string>
    <string name="sound_effects_credit">Credit for Sound Effects goes to PacDV and oblius
        (www.planetoblius.27south.com)
    </string>
    <string name="icon_with_initial_of_user">icon with initial of user</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="plus_icon">plus icon for adding friends</string>
    <string name="x_icon_content_description">X icon for refusing friend request or removing
        friend
    </string>
    <string name="arrow_icon_content_description">arrow icon for starting a decision with this
        friend
    </string>
    <string name="main_background_image_content_description">background image of person at
        crossroads unsure where to go
    </string>
    <string name="social_background_image_content_description">background image of a crowd of
        people
    </string>
    <string name="new_choice_bg_image_content_description">background image of signpost with
        excessive amount of signs
    </string>
    <string name="sound_icon_content_description">sound icon for muting and turning sound on
    </string>
    <string name="check_icon_content_description">check icon for accepting friend request</string>
    <string name="placeholder_for_image_content_description">placeholder for image of move
        selected
    </string>
    <string name="paper_content_description">pieces of paper</string>
    <string name="scissors_content_description">scissors</string>
    <string name="rock_content_description">a rock</string>
    <string name="solo_mode">Solo Mode</string>
    <string name="date_unknown">Date Unknown</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="enable_two_player_mode">- Enable two player mode!!</string>
    <string name="save_your_decisions">- Save your decisions!!!</string>
    <string name="browse_your_old_decisions">- Browse your old decisions!!!!</string>
    <string name="play_them_again">- Play them again!!!!!</string>
    <string name="connect_with_others">- Connect with others!</string>
    <string name="why_log_in">Why log in?!</string>
    <string name="sign_up_here">Don\'t have an account? Sign up here!</string>
    <string name="forgotten_password">Forgotten password? Reset it here!</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="choose_your_opponent">Choose Your Opponent</string>
    <string name="please_wait_a_moment">Please wait a moment</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email">Enter your email</string>
    <string name="round_history">Round History</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="decide_again">Decide Again</string>
    <string name="who_to_add">Who to add?</string>
    <string name="start_deciding">Start Deciding!</string>
    <string name="i_got_nothing">I got nothing</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="rps">RPS</string>
    <string name="add_friend_search_info">Search by username or email!</string>
    <string name="decide_now">Decide Now</string>
    <string name="choosing_between">Choosing between:</string>
    <string name="my_decisions">My Decisions</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="social">Social</string>
    <string name="and_with_space">and</string>
    <string name="vs">VS</string>
    <string name="add_people">Add People!</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="total_impartiality_mode">Total Impartiality Mode</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="go_solo">Go Solo</string>
    <string name="grab_a_friend">Grab a Friend</string>
    <string name="friend_requests">People who want to decide things with you</string>
    <string name="for_the_indecisive">for the indecisive</string>
    <string name="log_in_here">Already have an account? Log in here!</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="friends">People you are deciding things with</string>
    <string name="choose_move">Choose Move</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="empty_friend_list">looks like you need to find some people!</string>
    <string name="make_email_private">Make Email Private</string>
    <string name="opponent_label">Opponent: %s</string>
    <string name="bulleted_list">
        <li>as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;</li>\n
        <li>when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights,
            protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a
            government request;</li>\n
        <li>in the unlikely event that Manekej Apps iis involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale
            of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent
            notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well
            as any choices you may have regarding this information.
        </li>
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_date">Last updated: 3/6/2017</string>
    <string name="privacy_para_1">This privacy policy governs the use of the software application
        Indecisive RPS (“Application”) for mobile devices that was created by Manekej Apps.. The
        Application is a simple decision helper that uses Rock Paper Scissor to help the user make
        decisions with other users or by themselves.
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_para_2">This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection,
        use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Application.
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_para_3">We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving
        the Application. By using the Application, you agree to the collection and use of
        information in accordance with this policy.
    </string>
    <string name="information_collection_and_use">Information Collection And Use</string>
    <string name="information_collection_para_1">The Application obtains the information you provide
        when you download and register the Application. Registration is optional. However, please
        keep in mind that you may not be able to use some of the features offered by the Application
        unless you register.
    </string>
    <string name="information_collection_para_2">When you register with us and use the Application,
        you generally provide (a) an email address, user name, and password; (b) information you
        provide us when you contact us for help; (e) information you enter into our system when
        using the Application, i.e. the decisions that are being made.
    </string>
    <string name="log_data">Log Data</string>
    <string name="log_data_para_1">In addition to the above, the Application uses a third party
        service, FirebaseAnalytics, to collect certain information automatically, including, but not
        limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, the IP
        address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet
        browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application.
    </string>
    <string name="log_data_para_2">For more about what information FirebaseAnalytics collects,
        please see Firebase Help (https://support.google.com/firebase/answer/6318039) and Google’s
        Privacy Policy (https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
    </string>
    <string name="communications">Communications</string>
    <string name="communications_para">We may use the information you provided us to contact your
        from time to time to provide you with important information, required notices and marketing
        promotions.
    </string>
    <string name="third_party_access">Third-Party Access</string>
    <string name="third_party_para_1">We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected
        Information:
    </string>
    <string name="opt_out_rights">Opt-out rights</string>
    <string name="opt_out_para">You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily
        by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be
        available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or
        network. In addition you may opt out by checking the checkbox at the bottom of this page.
    </string>
    <string name="data_retention_policy">Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information</string>
    <string name="data_retention_para">We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the
        Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. If you’d like us to delete User Provided
        Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at manekejapps@gmail.com
        and we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided
        Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly.
    </string>
    <string name="children">Children</string>
    <string name="children_para">We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or
        market to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or
        her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact
        us manekejapps@gmail.com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable
        time.
    </string>
    <string name="your_consent">Your Consent</string>
    <string name="your_consent_para">By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing
        of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us.
        \'Processing,\' means using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited
        to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which
        activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the United States
        your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under United States privacy
        standards.
    </string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="security_para">The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but
        remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage,
        is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your
        Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
    </string>
    <string name="changes">Changes To This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="changes_para_1">This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 6, 2017 and will
        remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which
        will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
    </string>
    <string name="changes_para_2">We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any
        time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the
        Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute
        your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the
        modified Privacy Policy.
    </string>
    <string name="changes_para_3">If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will
        notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent
        notice on our application.
    </string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contact_us_para">If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please
        contact us.
    </string>
    <string name="opt_out_of_analytics">Opt out of analytics</string>
</resources>
